https://www.sassafras.com/privacy-notice/

+1 (603) 643-3351sales@sassafras.comMon - Fri: 8:30 - 6:00 EST
Search for:
EducationCorporateGovernmentSolutionsSupportDownloadsRelease AnnouncementsComponent HistoryTech BlogDocumentationTutorial VideosCompanyAboutNewsPartnersTestimonialsCase StudiesRequest a Live DemoContactEffective Date: January 1, 2019This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for Sassafras Software, Inc. (hereafter Sassafras) and our website; www.sassafras.com. This privacy notice applies to all data collected by Sassafras by any means from our customers. It serves to describe our business practices and to notify you of your rights and options.Information CollectedBy providing Sassafras with any data you agree with and consent to the terms of this policy. Information you provide to us may include business contact and financial information for the purpose of evaluating and purchasing our products and services. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone for any reason. We do not purchase, rent, or obtain private information from third parties. Business records are retained as part of our normal operations and as required for accounting and tax reporting. See Rights below for information on data deletion requests.We will use your information to communicate with you and to provide support for our products and services. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g., to process a credit card payment. All data is handled in the US by our servers and service providers (compliant with GDPR chapter 5).We may contact you via email or phone in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy. With your permission, we may direct a potential customer to you as a reference. In the normal course of business we may mention related customers to each other, but you can explicitly request to never be mentioned.Data collected by our PRS service and the handling of that data is detailed on our website at www.sassafras.com/hrl/7.7/prs.html.Your Access to and Control Over Information (Rights)You have the right to be informed of any changes to our data and privacy policies. Such changes will be publicly posted. You have the right to request disclosure of any and all information we have about you, and can do so by phone or email. You may request any information we retain be changed or corrected, and encourage you to give notice when such changes are needed to maintain communication and contract service. You may request deletion of any data at any time, and we will honor such requests that do not disrupt our business operations or data integrity. You may opt out of future contact that is not expressly related to fulfillment of contractual obligations by contacting us with such request. These rights are consistent and compliant with GDPR Chapter 3, and any items not mentioned are asserted as not applicable to our products and services.WebsiteWhen using our website forms to request a demo, quote, or evaluation, you are required to give certain information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact you about the products/services on our site in which you have expressed interest. At your option, you may also provide additional information about your environment, but it is not required.OrdersWe request information from you to purchase our products and services. To purchase from us, you must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we’ll use this information to contact you.SecuritySassafras takes precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon in your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page.While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (e.g. billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.CookiesSassafras uses “cookies” on our website. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to enter your email address more than once to access downloads, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track website traffic via analytics. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site. Other than Google analytics, we have no third party cookies or advertising of any kind on our website.LinksThe Sassafras web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.Notification of ChangesWhenever material changes are made to the privacy notice we will use the contact information we have on file to attempt to inform you. You may always request the current privacy statement.If you have any questions about this policy, wish to exercise your data protection rights, or feel that we are not abiding by the terms of this policy, please do not hesitate to contact us.Telephone: +1 (603) 643-3351 Email: info@sassafras.com Write to us at: Sassafras Software, Inc. PO Box 150 Hanover, NH 03755 USA Let's get in touchGive us a call or drop by anytime, we endeavour to answer all enquiries within 24 hours on business days. +1 (603) 643-3351 sales@sassafras.com ×Get started If you want to get a free consultation without any obligations, fill in the form below and we'll get in touch with you.
+1 (603) 643-3351
sales@sassafras.comLive Demo Name*
Last Organization*Email* PhoneNumber of computersPrimary interest / commentsSassafras will not share your personal information, period. We take privacy seriously. You may opt out of our communications at any time.
×
